http://www.cadig.com/aboutus/privacypolicy.php

Profile
Who is share-it!
Become an Affiliate
Why Join?
How Join?
Who
is share-it!
AutoTable
Fully import Excel files into AutoCAD (LT) / MicroStation and keep them updated easily.
AutoWord
Easily import Microsoft Word documents into AutoCAD (LT) / MicroStation and keep them updated.
Demo Online
Download
AutoWord FAQ
TableBuilder
Easily export the table in AutoCAD (LT) / MicroStation to Excel and convert the table drawn with lines and text to the AutoCAD native table.
AutoDatabase
Easily import Access database into AutoCAD and keep it updated.
Demo Online
Download
AutoDatabase FAQ
AutoField
Add many efficient fields to AutoCAD (LT). You can import a specific cell of the Excel file or a text format file as a field. Also you can count block or calculate the area and length of multiple objects as a field.
Demo Online
Download
AutoField FAQ
AutoScript (Freeware)
Run a set of commands to multiple drawings by simply specifying a script file and the list of drawings that you would like to apply the script to. It's compatible with AutoCAD 64-bit.
Demo Online
Download
Freeware Resources
AutoCAD Add-ons
PDF Tools
Home > About
Us> Privacy Policy
updated: Jun 5, 2005
Cadig is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy explains
data collection and use practices of the Cadig.com site (the "Site").
By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection
and use practices described in this privacy policy.
Collection of your Personal Information
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies
you (personal information) or allows us to contact you to provide a service
or carry out a transaction that you have requested such as receiving information
about Cadig products and services, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining
a limited-access service, signing up for an event or when purchasing,
downloading and/or registering Cadig products.
The Site may collect certain information about your visit, such as the
name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address
through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the
Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address
of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information
is used to help improve the Site, analyze trends, and administer the Site.
Use of your Personal Information
The personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate
the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s)
you have requested or authorized.
Cadig may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or
in the good faith belief.
Control of your Personal Information
Except as otherwise described in this policy, personal information you
provide on the Site will not be shared outside of Cadig and its controlled
subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission.
Cadig.com may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service
or security issues related to a product or service you requested, or confirming
you requested a product or service. In some services offered by Cadig.com,
contact with the customer is an intrinsic part of the service. You will
not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered
an essential part of the service(s) you have chosen.
Security of your Personal Information
Cadig is committed to protecting the security of your personal information.
We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect
your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.
For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer
servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities.
Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information (such as
a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use
of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Use of Cookies
We use cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the registration
process and to personalize the Site. A cookie is a small text file that
is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used
to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely
assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that
issued the cookie to you.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers
automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser
setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies,
you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this
or other Web sites you visit.
Enforcement of this Privacy Policy
If you have questions regarding this policy, you should contact Cadig.com.
Changes to this Policy
We may occasionally update this privacy policy. When we do, we will
also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy
policy. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to
stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information
we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement
to this privacy policy and any updates.
Contact Information
Cadig welcomes your comments regarding this privacy policy. If you believe
that Cadig has not adhered to this privacy policy, please contact Cadig.com.
© 2003-2020
Cadig Inc. All rights reserved - Privacy
Policy - AutoCAD - AutoCAD Excel - MicroStation - Site Map - Links
